grandcapital.net 2016-11-07

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy

Obligations of the Company
GRAND CAPITAL (further – the Company) is obliged to provide security and confidentiality of all
private information received from Clients. Confidentiality policy (further – Policy) explains how
the Company collects, uses and protects personal information of its Clients. If you are our
Client and documents provided are verified, then the present Policy does not require Clients to
provide any more information, aside of what is already provided to the Company. The question
of safety and security of personal information of our present and future Clients as well as
security of our web- site visitors has very high priority for us.
Information that we receive from our Clients
The Company has to receive the Client’s personal information in order to open a Demo or a Real
account. This information provides a better understanding of Client’s needs as well and helps
the Company to provide information about products and services that are the most suitable for
the Client. This information will also be used to raise the quality of consulting services for our
Clients about all questions that may arise.
Personal information received from the Client may include:
1.       Personal information that Clients indicate in statements, questionnaires and forms for
opening an account: First, Last and Middle name, address, birthdate, passport data, occupation
and position.
2.       Financial information such as your investment experience.
3.       Documents that are necessary for the Client’s identification: scan-copy of the passport,
utility bills and/or bank statements, foundation documents form the Client’s Company.
4.       Documents provided by Clients for verification of money transfer: money orders, bank
statements, credit card copies, etc.
The use of personal information

The Company may use Clients’ personal information in order to:
1. Verify Clients’ identity;
2. Quickly process Clients’ trading and non-trading transactions;
3. Promptly inform Clients about development of the list of Company’s products and services
   that we believe may interest our Clients.
4. Provide other services related to Clients’ trading accounts in the Company;
5. Keep a correct registration database with Clients’ accounts;
6. Analyze statistical data in order to offer products and services of higher quality to Clients;
   The Company keeps and uses personal information that Clients provide to the Company
   indefinitely.
Cookies
Cookies is a small fragment of data that is sent by the web-server to be stored on the user’s
computer in a form of a file, so with the next Client’s request web-site could extract this
information. This file is re-sent to the web-server in http-request every time when an attempt
to open a corresponding web-page is made. Cookies may be used on some pages of our
website to provide our Clients with the faster and more convenient access. Most of the web-
browsers allow rejecting Cookies if Clients don’t want them, while allowing to visit our website
without any restrictions. Cookies are not used for identification of our website visitors.
Third parties
The Company has the right to disclose Clients’ identity information to its affiliates, Company’s
agents or other trusted organizations and individuals (further – trustees) only with the purpose
of processing Clients trading and non-trading requests. The Company guarantees compliance
with this policy by its trustees as well as their acceptance of necessary measures to protect
Clients’ confidential information. The Company has the right to provide confidential information

about Clients’ personal data to the third parties that are not trustees of the Company only in
case if an official request from administrative or judicial body is received.
The Use of information
By registering an account in the Company Clients confirm that they agree with the use of
personal information according to the present Privacy Policy.
Contact information
We’ll be glad to answer any questions related to this Policy by email: info@grandcapital.net.
"This document is translated from the original written in Russian."
Please note that this document is translated from the original written in Russian. In case of
any discrepancies between the Russian and English versions of this document, the Russian
language version takes precedence.
"This document is translated from the original written in Russian."
Please note that this document is translated from the original written in Russian. In case of
any discrepancies between the Russian and English versions of this document, the Russian
language version takes precedence.
